<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Syracuse.io</title>
    <link>https://syracuse.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Syracuse.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 11:13:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://syracuse.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Again2</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/posts/welcome-again2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 11:13:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/posts/welcome-again2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/dev/drinks</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/groups/dev-drinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/groups/dev-drinks/</guid>
      <description>A happy hour series for developers in and around Syracuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>What is expected of me as a member of the Syracuse.io community Basically just be nice, treat others how you would like to be treated, and don&amp;rsquo;t be an garbage human being.
Code of Conduct Syracuse.io community a harassment free space. We do not tolerate harassment of any kind.
Harassment includes:
 Offensive comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, mental illness, physical appearance, body size, race, or religion Unwelcome comments regarding a person’s lifestyle choices and practices, including those related to food, health, parenting, drugs, and employment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/community/</guid>
      <description>The Syracuse developer community is centered around events by different groups.
We also send out a montly email (sign up here) and have an active group of locals in the SyracuseIO slack group. (Join the group!)
created to foster the software development community in Syracuse. We encourage sharing your knowledge, asking questions, building connections with a general ambition to strengthen the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack Upstate</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/groups/hackupstate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/groups/hackupstate/</guid>
      <description>We organize weekend hackathons twice a year (i.e. Fall &amp;amp; Spring) where developers, engineers and innovators from across Upstate New York come to Syracuse, NY, share ideas, form teams and build awesome projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenHack</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/openhacksyr.com</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/openhacksyr.com</guid>
      <description>A casual meetup based around developer side-projects. OpenHack meets the second tuesday of every month at Coworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack Chat</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/slack/</guid>
      <description>Join local Syracuse developers in the Syracuse Tech Slack group.
This is a place to discuss the local development scene, seek help, share advice, and discuss everything related to being a Software / Web / Tech person in Syracuse NY.
What is Slack? Slack is a chat application that simplifies communication communication between teams and, in our case, communities of like-minded folks
Slack chat spaces are divided into rooms called “channels”, and we have several set up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in coding</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/groups/women_in_coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/groups/women_in_coding/</guid>
      <description>Providing affordable coding classes for women in the community. Women in Coding host affordable monthly classes as well as casual events for people to network and connect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>syr(js)</title>
      <link>https://syracuse.io/groups/syrjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syracuse.io/groups/syrjs/</guid>
      <description>Syracuse javascript meetup group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>